<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Google Search for: bison</title>
<link>http://www.google.com/search?q=bison&amp;hl=en&amp;start=0</link><description>About 136,000,000 results</description><language>en</language><item><title>Bison - Wikipedia</title>
<link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bison</link><description>
Bison are large, even-toed ungulates in the genus Bison within the subfamily 
Bovinae. Two extant and six extinct species are recognised. Of the six extinct ...
</description></item><item><title>European bison - Wikipedia</title>
<link>https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/European_bison</link><description>
The European bison (Bison bonasus), also known as wisent or the European 
wood bison, is a Eurasian species of bison. It is one of two extant species of bison, ...
</description></item><item><title>bison | Facts | Britannica.com</title>
<link>https://www.britannica.com/animal/bison</link><description>
Bison, (genus Bison), also called buffalo or wisent, either of two species of oxlike 
grazing mammals that constitute the genus Bison of the family Bovidae.
</description></item><item><title>Basic Facts About Bison | Defenders of Wildlife</title>
<link>https://defenders.org/bison/basic-facts</link><description>
Millions of bison once thundered across North America. These massive animals, 
characterized by their long, shaggy brown coats, have poor eyesight but acute ...
</description></item><item><title>Bison Battle | Yellowstone | BBC Earth - YouTube</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/watch%3Fv%3DOLWQ59w1b58</link><description></description></item><item><title>Bison vs. Buffalo: What's the Difference? - YouTube</title>
<link>https://www.youtube.com/watch%3Fv%3D45CuH-QZ1i4</link><description></description></item><item><title>Return of the bison: herd makes surprising comeback on Dutch ...</title>
<link>https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2018/may/28/return-of-the-bison-herd-makes-surprising-comeback-on-dutch-coast</link><description>28 May 2018 ... Eighty years after they were hunted to extinction, the successful reintroduction of 
a herd of wild European bison on to the dunes of the Dutch ...</description></item><item><title>How Native American tribes are bringing back the bison from brink ...</title>
<link>https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2018/dec/12/how-native-american-tribes-are-bringing-back-the-bison-from-brink-of-extinction</link><description>12 Dec 2018 ... On 5,000 hectares of unploughed prairie in north-eastern Montana, hundreds of 
wild bison roam once again. But this herd is not in a national ...</description></item><item><title>American Bison | National Geographic</title>
<link>https://www.nationalgeographic.com/animals/mammals/a/american-bison/</link><description>
Bison stand some 5 to 6.5 feet tall at the shoulder, and can tip the scales at over a 
ton. Despite their massive size, bison are quick on their feet. When the need ...
</description></item><item><title>It's Bison, Not Buffalo. And Other American Bison Facts ...</title>
<link>https://nationalzoo.si.edu/animals/news/its-bison-not-buffalo-and-other-american-bison-facts</link><description>
23 Aug 2018 ... The iconic song of the American West, “Home on the Range,” got a key detail 
wrong — buffalo never roamed the region! But bison still do.
</description></item><item><title>BBC - Earth - Bison had survived for 2 million years until humans ...</title>
<link>http://www.bbc.com/earth/story/20170406-bison-had-survived-for-2-million-years-until-humans-arrived</link><description>
7 Apr 2017 ... The American bison was voted America's national mammal in May 2016. The 
decision, while largely symbolic, offered support to conservation ...
</description></item><item><title>Bison are back, and that benefits many other species on the Great ...</title>
<link>http://theconversation.com/bison-are-back-and-that-benefits-many-other-species-on-the-great-plains-107588</link><description>
18 Jan 2019 ... Bison once dominated the Great Plains but were nearly wiped out by hunters in 
the 1800s. Now scientists are learning that bison's presence ...
</description></item><item><title>Yellowstone Bison - Yellowstone National Park (U.S. National Park ...</title>
<link>https://www.nps.gov/yell/learn/nature/bison.htm</link><description>
7 Mar 2019 ... Yellowstone preserves the most important bison herd in the United States. Learn 
more about the near extinction and recovery of these ...
</description></item><item><title>Bison - GNU Project - Free Software Foundation - GNU.org</title>
<link>https://www.gnu.org/software/bison/</link><description>
6 Aug 2014 ... Bison is a general-purpose parser generator that converts an annotated context-
free grammar into a deterministic LR or generalized LR (GLR) ...
</description></item><item><title>bison - Wiktionary</title>
<link>https://en.wiktionary.org/wiki/bison</link><description>
Akin to Old High German wisunt (“bison”), German Wisent (“bison”), Old English 
wesend, wusend (“bison, buffalo, wild ox”), Middle Dutch wēsent (“wild ox”).
</description></item><item><title>Bison - Rewilding Britain</title>
<link>https://www.rewildingbritain.org.uk/rewilding/reintroductions/bison</link><description>
Date of disappearance: Between 15,000 and 25,000 years ago. Reason: Climatic 
changes. Special power: They help to maintain a mosaic of habitats: a mixture ...
</description></item><item><title>Bison Bison Bison: America's New National Mammal | The New Yorker</title>
<link>https://www.newyorker.com/tech/annals-of-technology/bison-bison-bison-americas-new-national-mammal</link><description>13 May 2016 ... On Monday, President Obama signed legislation honoring the American bison, 
also known as the buffalo, as this country's first national ...</description></item><item><title>What bison in South Dakota can teach us about fighting climate ...</title>
<link>https://www.vox.com/energy-and-environment/2018/2/2/16934232/holistic-grazing-bison-south-dakota-climate-change</link><description>
2 Feb 2018 ... One that really stood out was about South Dakota — a part of the country often 
overlooked for its climate vulnerability — tying together bison ...
</description></item><item><title>The Bison Returns to the Great American Plains | Science ...</title>
<link>https://www.smithsonianmag.com/science-nature/bison-returns-wilds-america-180970547/</link><description>
This Winter, if all goes as planned, a caravan of livestock trucks will carry dozens 
of American bison out of Yellowstone National Park on a 500-mile journey into ...
</description></item><item><title>What bison in South Dakota can teach us about fighting climate ...</title>
<link>https://www.vox.com/energy-and-environment/2018/2/2/16934232/holistic-grazing-bison-south-dakota-climate-change</link><description>
2 Feb 2018 ... One that really stood out was about South Dakota — a part of the country often 
overlooked for its climate vulnerability — tying together bison ...
</description></item><item><title>Six Pure Bison Calves Born at WCS's Bronx Zoo &gt; Newsroom</title>
<link>https://newsroom.wcs.org/News-Releases/articleType/ArticleView/articleId/10058/Six-Pure-Bison-Calves-Born-at-WCSs-Bronx-Zoo.aspx</link><description>
12 May 2017 ... BRONX, NEW YORK – May 12, 2017 – Six American bison calves have been born at WCS’s (Wildlife Conservation Society) Bronx Zoo and four of them are now on exhibit on the zoo’s Bison Range.
 The calves will help the Bronx Zoo further bison conservation efforts.
</description></item><item><title>The Bison Returns to the Great American Plains | Science ...</title>
<link>https://www.smithsonianmag.com/science-nature/bison-returns-wilds-america-180970547/</link><description>
This Winter, if all goes as planned, a caravan of livestock trucks will carry dozens 
of American bison out of Yellowstone National Park on a 500-mile journey into ...
</description></item><item><title>Bison | Wildwood Trust</title>
<link>https://wildwoodtrust.org/wildwood-kent/animals/bison</link><description>
Bison. Bison bonasus. The European Bison, or Wisent is the largest terrestrial 
animal in Europe and once roamed from southern Britain as far as Russia but ...
</description></item><item><title>Bison | The power of adhesives.</title>
<link>https://www.bison.net/</link><description>
Bison products offer the best solutions for bonding or sealing paper and 
cardboard, leather, fabric and wood, as well as for joining metal and plastic. In 
the home ...
</description></item><item><title>Mexico ranch helps American bison make a comeback - Phys.org</title>
<link>https://phys.org/news/2018-09-mexico-ranch-american-bison-comeback.html</link><description>
19 Sep 2018 ... Hundreds of years ago, the American bison roamed freely across the widest 
natural range of any herbivore on the continent—a vast habitat ...
</description></item><item><title>It's official: America's first national mammal is the bison - The ...</title>
<link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/animalia/wp/2016/04/27/how-the-bison-once-nearing-extinction-lived-to-become-americas-national-mammal/</link><description></description></item><item><title>Facts About Bison - Live Science</title>
<link>https://www.livescience.com/60241-bison-facts.html</link><description>
25 Aug 2017 ... The American bison is the official mammal of the United States and is the largest 
mammal in North America.
</description></item><item><title>European Bison Reservation (Bialowieza) - 2019 All You Need to ...</title>
<link>https://www.tripadvisor.co.uk/Attraction_Review-g274740-d4087179-Reviews-European_Bison_Reservation-Bialowieza_Podlaskie_Province_Eastern_Poland.html</link><description>We went hiking into the primal forest but did not see wildlife there because the 
animals are very shy. So we decided to visit this reserve to get an up close look at
 ...</description></item><item><title>BBC Radio Wales - Bison - Country Focus, Organics, Bison and ...</title>
<link>https://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/p03m8l2g/p03m4qr9</link><description>
Farming Bison. Another bright idea from Lord Newborough for Farm Manager 
Gareth Jones to deal with. The Farm Shop · Fruit 'n Veg · Chicks · Listening 
intently.
</description></item><item><title>BISON | meaning in the Cambridge English Dictionary</title>
<link>https://dictionary.cambridge.org/dictionary/english/bison</link><description>
bison definition: 1. a large wild animal, similar to a cow but having a larger head 
and shoulders covered in hair, found in North America and Europe. The North ...
</description></item><item><title>Man taunts charging bison - CNN Video - CNN.com</title>
<link>https://edition.cnn.com/videos/us/2018/08/03/man-taunts-bison-yellowstone-national-park-hln-vpx.hln</link><description></description></item><item><title>Opinion | The Bison Roundup the Government Wants to Hide - The ...</title>
<link>https://www.nytimes.com/2016/02/15/opinion/the-bison-roundup-the-government-wants-to-hide.html</link><description>
15 Feb 2016 ... THE National Park Service is set to begin its annual roundup of wild bison in 
Yellowstone National Park today. A portion will be slaughtered to ...
</description></item><item><title>Extermination of the American Bison - American Memory Timeline ...</title>
<link>http://www.loc.gov/teachers/classroommaterials/presentationsandactivities/presentations/timeline/riseind/west/bison.html</link><description>
William T. Hornady reports on market hunters extermination of the American Bison from an excerpt of Evolution of the Conservation Movement.
</description></item><item><title>European Bison | Highland Wildlife Park</title>
<link>http://www.highlandwildlifepark.org.uk/animals-attractions/animals/european-bison/</link><description>
The European bison (Bison bonasus), is similar in appearance to its North 
American relative (Bison bison) but is smaller in size.
</description></item><item><title>The Remarkable Story of How the Bison Returned to Europe – Cool ...</title>
<link>https://blog.nature.org/science/2017/08/22/remarkable-story-how-bison-returned-europe/</link><description>
22 Aug 2017 ... Yes, the bison roams across Europe. And the story of its conservation rescue may 
be even more dramatic than that of its American counterpart.
</description></item><item><title>Bison — Knepp Wildland</title>
<link>https://knepp.co.uk/bison</link><description>
Bison. The European bison, the largest herbivore in Europe, went extinct in the 
wild in the early 20th century due to habitat degradation and fragmentation, forest
 ...
</description></item><item><title>Bison Coffee House - Home | Facebook</title>
<link>https://en-gb.facebook.com/bisoncoffeeyork/</link><description>
Cheers to James Arden for this lovely promo video. He's actually managed to 
catch me doing some work which is an achievement on it's own! Ta! 30. 1. Bison
 ...
</description></item><item><title>Basingstoke Bison (@BisonHockey) | Twitter</title>
<link>https://twitter.com/bisonhockey%3Flang%3Den</link><description>
The latest Tweets from Basingstoke Bison (@BisonHockey). The Official Twitter 
Account of the @TraneUK sponsored Basingstoke Bison - 2017/18 NIHL 1 South
 ...
</description></item><item><title>Basingstoke Bison | Welcome to Basingstoke Bison</title>
<link>http://www.bstokebison.co.uk/</link><description>
Final Score: Invicta Dynamos 1 Trane Basingstoke Bison 2. By Nigel Simmonds 
Ref: Stephenson Lino's: Miss Lack &amp; Pullar MoM Dynamos: Morris MoM Bison: ...
</description></item><item><title>Bison Golf Club</title>
<link>http://bisongolf.net/</link><description>
Situated high in the majestic White Mountains in Show Low, Arizona, just about 
three hours from either Phoenix or Tucson, is the beautiful Bison Golf Club, ...
</description></item><item><title>Bison | Board Game | BoardGameGeek</title>
<link>https://boardgamegeek.com/boardgame/32/bison</link><description>
Buffalo, one player represents Indians who are trying to keep the village from being overrun by buffalo.
 This player moves the Indian chief and his dogs while the other player takes charge of the herd of rampaging buffalo, all of which are represented by nice little wooden pieces.
</description></item><item><title>How bison help shape the Northern Great Plains | Pages | WWF</title>
<link>https://www.worldwildlife.org/pages/how-bison-help-shape-the-northern-great-plains</link><description>
Bison play an enormous role in shaping the ecology of the Northern Great Plains, 
impacting everything from plants to pronghorn. Explore their influence and ...
</description></item><item><title>Apple Cider Bison Bone Broth - 6 Pack Bison Broth - EPIC – EPIC ...</title>
<link>https://epicprovisions.com/products/bison-apple-cider-bone-broth-holiday-exclusive</link><description>
EPIC takes pride in slow cooking our bones to extract maximum nutrient rich 
collagen, minerals and gelatin. Try the Apple Cider Bison Bone Broth now!
</description></item><item><title>Printed Graphics for Brand Communication | BISON Print Ltd</title>
<link>https://www.madebybison.co.uk/</link><description>
As one of the UK's leading producers of digital print and large format graphic 
solutions, being MadeByBison comes with a guarantee of the highest quality.
</description></item><item><title>Burrito Bison - Play it now at Coolmath-Games.com</title>
<link>https://www.coolmathgames.com/0-burrito-bison</link><description>
Burrito Bison at Cool Math Games: Smash all of the gummy bears with your 
mighty luchador skills! Rack up huge combos to buy upgrades and escape 
Candy ...
</description></item><item><title>The Bison Grill | Rhug Estate Organic Farm</title>
<link>https://rhug.co.uk/dining/the-bison-grill</link><description>
Next to the Farm Shop, our award-winning Bison Grill offers dining. Our chef has 
created a Menu with a focus local products &amp; our organic meat where possible.
</description></item><item><title>bison — Homebrew Formulae</title>
<link>https://formulae.brew.sh/formula/bison</link><description>
bison, 16,623. Installs on Request (30 days). bison, 11,185. Build Errors (30 days
). bison, 8. Installs (90 days). bison, 47,571. Installs on Request (90 days).
</description></item><item><title>15 Facts About Our National Mammal: The American Bison | U.S. ...</title>
<link>https://www.doi.gov/blog/15-facts-about-our-national-mammal-american-bison</link><description>
9 May 2016 ... On May 9, 2016, President Obama signed the National Bison Legacy Act into law
, officially making the American bison the national mammal of ...
</description></item><item><title>Debian -- Package Search Results -- bison</title>
<link>https://packages.debian.org/bison</link><description>
You have searched for packages that names contain bison in all suites, all 
sections, and all architectures. Found 12 matching packages.
</description></item><item><title>bison — Homebrew Formulae</title>
<link>https://formulae.brew.sh/formula/bison</link><description>
bison, 16,623. Installs on Request (30 days). bison, 11,185. Build Errors (30 days
). bison, 8. Installs (90 days). bison, 47,571. Installs on Request (90 days).
</description></item><item><title>15 Facts About Our National Mammal: The American Bison | U.S. ...</title>
<link>https://www.doi.gov/blog/15-facts-about-our-national-mammal-american-bison</link><description>
9 May 2016 ... On May 9, 2016, President Obama signed the National Bison Legacy Act into law
, officially making the American bison the national mammal of ...
</description></item><item><title>Debian -- Package Search Results -- bison</title>
<link>https://packages.debian.org/bison</link><description>
You have searched for packages that names contain bison in all suites, all 
sections, and all architectures. Found 12 matching packages.
</description></item><item><title>Bison | IUCN</title>
<link>https://www.iucn.org/commissions/ssc-groups/mammals/specialist-groups-a-e/bison</link><description>
IUCN SSC Bison Specialist Group Chair: Glenn Plumb EuropeNorth America 
Europe Red List Authority Coordinators: Wanda Olech The purpose of the IUCN 
S..
</description></item><item><title>Bison for Windows - GnuWin32</title>
<link>http://gnuwin32.sourceforge.net/packages/bison.htm</link><description>
Bison is a general purpose parser generator that converts a grammar description 
for an LALR(1) context-free grammar into a C program to parse that grammar.
</description></item><item><title>BISON: Music</title>
<link>https://bison.bandcamp.com/</link><description>
BISON. Vancouver, British Columbia. With whatever trust of panic we went out 
with, so much we shall return. European tour with guests LLNN. April/May 2018.
</description></item><item><title>Bison IGS VR600.01 - V12</title>
<link>http://v12footwear.com/product/bison-igs-vr600-01/</link><description>
Constructed from a polished full grain leather upper, the new and improved Bison 
has a cut away scoop collar for easy foot access and comfort. Lightweight ...
</description></item><item><title>Bison – Gallaudet University</title>
<link>https://www.gallaudet.edu/gallaudet-technology-services/services/bison</link><description>
Welcome to the landing page for Gallaudet University's PeopleSoft, also known 
as Bison, Campus Community, Human Resources, and Student Administration ...
</description></item><item><title>Bison Are Helping Rewild the Last of the Midwest's Prairies</title>
<link>https://earther.gizmodo.com/bison-are-helping-rewild-the-last-of-the-midwests-prair-1829693894</link><description>
31 Oct 2018 ... When white settlers first arrived, a large swath of the U.S. was blanketed in 
tallgrass prairie. But turmoil came to the landscape shortly thereafter ...
</description></item><item><title>Bison Brewing</title>
<link>http://bisonbrew.com/</link><description>
Support what you love. Farmers and brewers share your vision to live free of 
harmful ingredients. Organic beer is Non-Toxic and Sustainable. A 6-pack a 
week is ...
</description></item><item><title>Bison | Free Listening on SoundCloud</title>
<link>https://soundcloud.com/bisonvt</link><description>
Before the east indians. Maybe even. Burlington, VT. 15 Tracks. 113 Followers. 
Stream Tracks and Playlists from Bison on your desktop or mobile device.
</description></item><item><title>Bison Returned From the Brink Just in Time for Climate Change ...</title>
<link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/features/2017-07-31/bison-returned-from-the-brink-just-in-time-for-climate-change</link><description>
31 Jul 2017 ... Turner's bison don't need much human intervention to thrive. They breed 
naturally in the early summer, when the grass is at its most nutritious, ...
</description></item><item><title>National Bison Association: Home Page</title>
<link>https://bisoncentral.com/</link><description>
Deliciously Healthy Bison · Humane Production of Bison ... Where to Buy Bison 
Meat · Bison Recipes ... Bison is Nature's Perfect Protein · Buying Bison in Bulk.
</description></item><item><title>Bison Cam - Watering Hole at Grasslands National Park | Explore.org</title>
<link>https://explore.org/livecams/bison/plains-bison-grasslands-national-park-cam-1</link><description>
Live video of bison, commonly called buffalo, at a watering hole in Grasslands 
National Park in Canada. Bison cam captures a glimpse into life at the park.
</description></item><item><title>European Bison or Wisent | New Forest Wildlife Park</title>
<link>http://www.newforestwildlifepark.co.uk/animals/mammals/european-bison-or-wisent/</link><description>
Meet Janek, Wotjek and Leszek our three European Bison. European bison are 
surprisingly agile and can clear 3m wide streams from a standing start.
</description></item><item><title>Brave Bison | LinkedIn</title>
<link>https://www.linkedin.com/company/brave-bison</link><description>Learn about working at Brave Bison. Join LinkedIn today for free. See who you 
know at Brave Bison, leverage your professional network, and get hired.</description></item><item><title>Bison Slaughter's Destructive Legacy for Native Americans | Inside ...</title>
<link>https://www.insidescience.org/news/bison-slaughter%25E2%2580%2599s-destructive-legacy-native-americans</link><description>
1 Mar 2018 ... (Inside Science) -- In 1870, there were at least 10 million bison in the southern 
herd on the North American plains. Fewer than 20 years later, ...
</description></item><item><title>Last Bison</title>
<link>https://www.thelastbison.com/</link><description>
In 2012 The Last Bison seemingly rose from the marshes of southeastern Virginia 
to captivate the national music scene with a rare blend of music that NPR ...
</description></item><item><title>Bison Coffee, York - Restaurant Reviews, Phone Number &amp; Photos ...</title>
<link>https://www.tripadvisor.co.uk/Restaurant_Review-g186346-d3502104-Reviews-Bison_Coffee-York_North_Yorkshire_England.html</link><description>
Bison Coffee, York: See 46 unbiased reviews of Bison Coffee, rated 4.5 of 5 on 
TripAdvisor and ranked #302 of 861 restaurants in York.
</description></item><item><title>Bison Studio | Digital Product Studio</title>
<link>https://bison.studio/</link><description>
Bison Studio is a digital product studio based in Malta. We offer a specialized 
service in UX Design, Web Design, App Design, and Web Development.
</description></item></channel></rss>